<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8">
<title>Privacy Policy</title>
<meta name="title" content="Privacy Policy ">
<meta name="DC.title" lang="en" content="Privacy Policy ">
<meta name="description" content=""Expert concrete driveway installation in Ann Arbor, MI. High-quality, durable, and aesthetically pleasing solutions.""Select the best contractor in Ann Arbor, MI for your concrete driveway installation. Make a sturdy and long-lasting choice.""Explore the cost of concrete driveway installation in Ann Arbor, MI. Affordable, quality solutions for your home.""Discover permit requirements for installing a concrete driveway in Ann Arbor, MI. Ensure your project complies with local regulations.""Explore the process and timeline of concrete driveway installation in Ann Arbor, MI. Quality service guaranteed!""Explore various types of concrete used in driveways at Concrete Driveway Ann Arbor Mi. Enhance your home's curb appeal today!""Expert maintenance & repair services for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, Mi. Enhance your driveway's longevity and aesthetic appeal.""Boost your Concrete Driveway's longevity in Ann Arbor, MI with our effective preventive maintenance tips for durability.""Explore common causes for concrete driveway damage in Ann Arbor, MI. Protect your investment with timely repairs and maintenance.""Top-rated concrete driveway repair services in Ann Arbor, MI. Professional, reliable companies ensuring quality results.""Compare DIY vs professional repairs for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Make an informed choice for durability & savings.""Explore the expenses of repairing a concrete driveway in Ann Arbor, MI. Get detailed pricing on local services.""Explore diverse designs and styles for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Enhance your home's curb appeal with our quality solutions.""Explore popular design trends for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Enhance curb appeal with stylish, durable designs.""Choose your concrete driveway design in Ann Arbor, Mi wisely, considering climate factors for durability and style.""Experience unique concrete driveway customizations in Ann Arbor, MI. Enhance your home's curb appeal today!""Explore how home architecture impacts driveway design in Ann Arbor, MI. Discover unique concrete driveway solutions.""Explore stamped, stained & decorative concrete driveway options in Ann Arbor MI. Boost curb appeal with stylish designs.""Explore the environmental impact of concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Understand sustainability and eco-friendly options.""Explore how concrete driveway production in Ann Arbor, MI impacts carbon footprint. Learn to choose eco-friendly solutions.""Explore sustainable materials for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor MI. Enhancing durability and environmental friendliness.""Explore eco-friendly drainage solutions for your Concrete Driveway in Ann Arbor Mi, minimizing environmental impact.""Learn about Ann Arbor Mi's local regulations for eco-friendly concrete driveways. Go green, stay compliant!""Explore porous pavement for your concrete driveway in Ann Arbor, MI. Enhance drainage, reduce runoff & increase sustainability.""Explore eco-friendly, durable alternatives to concrete driveways in Ann Arbor Mi. Enhance your curb appeal today!""Explore the pros and cons of Asphalt driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Compare them with Concrete driveways for an informed choice.""Explore paver stone driveways in Ann Arbor, MI. Learn their benefits and drawbacks versus concrete options.""Opt for gravel or crushed stone, a durable & cost-effective alternative for concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI.""Compare costs of different driveway materials in Ann Arbor, MI. Find the most cost-effective solution for your concrete driveway.""Explore Resinbound surfaces, an emerging technology for durable, appealing concrete driveways in Ann Arbor, MI."">
<meta name="robots" content="index, follow">
<meta name="googlebot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<meta name="bingbot" content="index, follow, max-snippet:-1, max-image-preview:large, max-video-preview:-1">
<link rel="canonical" href="privacy-policy.html">
<link rel="shortcut icon"  href="img/waltzlogo3-410w.jpg"/>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/css/bootstrap.min.css">
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://fonts.googleapis.com/css?family=Poppins:100,200,300,400,500,600,700,800,900&amp;display=swap" as="style" onload="this.onload=null;this.rel='stylesheet'">
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/jquery@3.5.1/dist/jquery.slim.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/popper.js@1.16.1/dist/umd/popper.min.js"></script>
<script src="https://cdn.jsdelivr.net/npm/bootstrap@4.6.1/dist/js/bootstrap.bundle.min.js"></script>
<link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css">
<style type="text/css"> 
a{
text-decoration: none!important;
}
*{
font-family: 'Poppins', sans-serif;
}
.nav-link{
color: #141414 !important;
}
.y55f7b5da6598b8beb377675ed43d2faf i:hover{
background: black;
color:#ffdde1;
border-radius: 50%;
width:10mm;
text-align:center;
height:10mm;
}
.a3c6a8a1dca0c007217940235cf0f3d82{
background-color:#fe5270!important;
border-color:#fe5270!important;
color:#ffffff!important;
}
li a{
color: #ff626b;
}
footer *{
font-size:19px!important;
color:#7c7c7c!important;
line-height: 1.5;
}
.y55f7b5da6598b8beb377675ed43d2faf i{
border-radius: 50%;
width: 10mm;
text-align: center;
line-height: 37px;
height: 10mm;
}
ul{
list-style: circle;
}
.align-self-stretch{
ms-flex-item-align: stretch!important;
align-self: stretch!important;
}
.underline .line{
width: 5rem;
height: 3px;
background: linear-gradient(90deg, #a48efe,#ff646d);
display: inline-block;
}
.t1f1e75d30d8a7bdeccb15c3cf4607e85 *{
color:white!important;
}
.nav-item{
margin-top: 9.5px;
margin-bottom: 10.5px;
padding-left: 6.9px;
padding-right: 7.2px;
}
.t1f1e75d30d8a7bdeccb15c3cf4607e85{
background: rgba(0,0,0,0.6);
text-align: center;
}
.navbar a{
font-size: 18.4px;
}
footer ul{
padding-left: 0px!important;
list-style: none;
}
.cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d:hover{
background-size: 100% 100%!important;
color:!important;
background:!important;
background-repeat: no-repeat!important;
background-position: 0 90%!important; 
transition: background-size 0.2s ease-in!important;
}
.btn-md{
padding:15px 30.4px;
border-radius: 0;
}
footer a{
color:  #7c7c7c!important;
text-decoration: underline!important;
}
footer{
padding-top:60.3px;
padding-bottom:60.1px;
}
.e6b772e501258e8a125ae88d0c0fd6601{
text-decoration: underline!important;
}
.y55f7b5da6598b8beb377675ed43d2faf{
font-size:19.6px;
padding:9.9px;
color: black;
}
.display-2{
font-size: 45.3px;
}
</style>
</head>
<body>
<nav class="navbar navbar-expand-lg">
<a class="navbar-brand" href="index.html"  >

<img alt="" src="img/waltzlogo3-410w.jpg"  width="100px" ></a>
<button class="navbar-toggler" type="button" data-toggle="collapse" data-target="#navbarSupportedContent" aria-controls="navbarSupportedContent" aria-expanded="false" aria-label="Toggle navigation">
<span class="navbar-toggler-icon"></span>
</button><div class="collapse navbar-collapse" id="navbarSupportedContent">
<ul class="ml-auto navbar-nav align-items-center">
<li class="nav-item" ><a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d nav-link" href="news.html" rel="nofollow">News</a></li>
<li class=" dropdown nav-item"><a class="dropdown-toggle cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d nav-link" href="index.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Concrete Driveway Installation Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown"><a class="dropdown-item" href="index.html"  >Concrete Driveway Installation Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="choosing-the-right-contractor-for-installation.html"  >Choosing the right contractor for installation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="cost-of-concrete-driveway-installation-in-ann-arbor.html"  >Cost of concrete driveway installation in Ann Arbor</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="permit-requirements-for-driveway-installation-in-ann-arbor.html"  >Permit requirements for driveway installation in Ann Arbor</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="the-process-and-timeline-of-concrete-driveway-installation.html"  >The process and timeline of concrete driveway installation</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="different-types-of-concrete-used-in-driveways.html"  >Different types of concrete used in driveways</a>
<li class="dropdown nav-item "><a class="dropdown-toggle nav-link cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="maintenance-and-repair-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Maintenance and Repair of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu dropdown-menu-right" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown"><a class="dropdown-item" href="maintenance-and-repair-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html"  >Maintenance and Repair of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="preventive-maintenance-tips-for-durability.html"  >Preventive maintenance tips for durability</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="common-causes-for-concrete-driveway-damage.html"  >Common causes for concrete driveway damage</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="professional-companies-offering-repair-services-in-ann-arbor.html"  >Professional companies offering repair services in Ann Arbor</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="doityourself-versus-professional-repairs.html"  >Doityourself versus professional repairs</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="costs-associated-with-repairing-a-concrete-driveway.html"  >Costs associated with repairing a concrete driveway</a>
<li class=" nav-item dropdown"><a class="nav-link dropdown-toggle cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="designs-and-styles-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Designs and Styles of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown"><a class="dropdown-item" href="designs-and-styles-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html"  >Designs and Styles of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="popular-design-trends-for-driveways.html"  >Popular design trends for driveways</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="considering-climate-factors-when-choosing-a-design-or-style.html"  >Considering climate factors when choosing a design or style</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="unique-customizations-available-for-concrete-driveways.html"  >Unique customizations available for concrete driveways</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="influence-of-home-architecture-on-driveway-design.html"  >Influence of home architecture on driveway design</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="stamped-stained-and-decorative-options.html"  >Stamped stained and decorative options</a>
<li class="dropdown nav-item "><a class="dropdown-toggle cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d nav-link" href="environmental-impact-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Environmental Impact of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown"><a class="dropdown-item" href="environmental-impact-of-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html"  >Environmental Impact of Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="carbon-footprint-associated-with-concrete-production.html"  >Carbon footprint associated with concrete production</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="use-of-sustainable-materials-in-concrete-driveways.html"  >Use of sustainable materials in concrete driveways</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="drainage-considerations-to-reduce-environmental-impact.html"  >Drainage considerations to reduce environmental impact</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="local-regulations-regarding-environmentally-friendly-driveways.html"  >Local regulations regarding environmentally friendly driveways</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="potential-use-of-permeable-or-porous-pavement.html"  >Potential use of permeable or porous pavement</a>
<li class=" nav-item dropdown"><a class="dropdown-toggle cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d nav-link" href="alternatives-to-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html" id="navbarDropdown" role="button" data-toggle="dropdown" aria-expanded="false">Alternatives to Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<div class="dropdown-menu-right dropdown-menu" aria-labelledby="navbarDropdown"><a class="dropdown-item" href="alternatives-to-concrete-driveways-in-ann-arbor-mi.html"  >Alternatives to Concrete Driveways in Ann Arbor Mi</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="asphalt-driveways-and-their-proscons.html"  >Asphalt driveways and their proscons</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="paver-stone-driveways-and-their-benefitsdrawbacks.html"  >Paver stone driveways and their benefitsdrawbacks</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="gravel-or-crushed-stone-as-an-alternative-option.html"  >Gravel or crushed stone as an alternative option</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="comparing-costs-between-different-driveway-materials.html"  >Comparing costs between different driveway materials</a>
<a class="dropdown-item" href="resinbound-surfaces-as-emerging-technology.html"  >Resinbound surfaces as emerging technology</a>
<li class="nav-item">
<a class="nav-link cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow" >About Us</a></li>
<li class="nav-item"><a class="btn btn-md a3c6a8a1dca0c007217940235cf0f3d82" href="https://www.waltzconcrete.com/contact" rel="nofollow">Contact Us</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
</nav>
<div>
<section class="container">
<h1>Privacy Policy for Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI</h1>
<p>At Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors.
This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI and how we use it. You can check out our main website here: https://www.waltzconcrete.com/</p>
<p>If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.</p>
<p>This Privacy Policy only applies to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website. </p>
<h2>Consent</h2>
<p>By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.</p>
<h2>Information we collect</h2>
<p>The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.</p>
<p>If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, email address, phone number, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.</p>
<p>When you register for an Account, we may ask for your contact information, including items such as name, Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI, address, email address, and telephone number.</p>
<h2>How we use your information</h2>
<p>We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:</p>
<ul>
<li>Provide, operate, and maintain our website</li>
<li>Improve, personalize, and expand our website</li>
<li>Understand and analyze how you use our website</li>
<li>Develop new products, services, features, and functionality</li>
<li>Communicate with you, either directly or through one of our partners, including for customer service, to provide you with updates and other information relating to the website, and for marketing and promotional purposes</li>
<li>Send you emails</li>
<li>Find and prevent fraud</li>
</ul>
<h2>Log Files</h2>
<p>Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.</p>
<h2>Advertising Partners Privacy Policies</h2>
<P>You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI.</p>
<p>Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.</p>
<p>Note that Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.</p>
<h2>Third Party Privacy Policies</h2>
<p>Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. </p>
<p>You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.</p>
<h2>CCPA Privacy Rights (Do Not Sell My Personal Information)</h2>
<p>Under the CCPA, among other rights, California consumers have the right to:</p>
<p>Request that a business that collects a consumer's personal data disclose the categories and specific pieces of personal data that a business has collected about consumers.</p>
<p>Request that a business delete any personal data about the consumer that a business has collected.</p>
<p>Request that a business that sells a consumer's personal data, not sell the consumer's personal data.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>GDPR Data Protection Rights</h2>
<p>We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights. Every user is entitled to the following:</p>
<p>The right to access – You have the right to request copies of your personal data. We may charge you a small fee for this service.</p>
<p>The right to rectification – You have the right to request that we correct any information you believe is inaccurate. You also have the right to request that we complete the information you believe is incomplete.</p>
<p>The right to erasure – You have the right to request that we erase your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to restrict processing – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to object to processing – You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>The right to data portability – You have the right to request that we transfer the data that we have collected to another organization, or directly to you, under certain conditions.</p>
<p>If you make a request, we have one month to respond to you. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please contact us.</p>
<h2>Children's Information</h2>
<p>Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.</p>
<p>Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.</p>
<h2>Publisher</h2>
<p>
This website is owned and published by:
Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI</br>
(517) 605-8184</br>
</br>
Ann Arbor MI</br>
</br>
https://www.waltzconcrete.com/</br>
info@waltzconcrete.com</br>
</p>
</section>
</div> 
<footer>
<div class="container">
<div class="row align-center justify-content-center"><div class="col-md-3">
<div class="text-dark">
<ul><li>Waltz Concrete Ann Arbor MI</li><li>Phone : (517) 605-8184</li>
<li>Email : info@waltzconcrete.com</li>
<li>City : Ann Arbor MI</li>
<li><a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="https://maps.app.goo.gl/wU6i1ZVE2QbFCa8j9" rel="nofollow"> Google Business Profile</a></li>
<li>Company Website : <a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d"  href="https://www.waltzconcrete.com/" >https://www.waltzconcrete.com/</a></li>
</ul>
</div>
</div> 
<div class="col-md-3">
<ul>
<li><a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="sitemap.html" rel="nofollow">Sitemap</a></li>
<li><a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="privacy-policy.html" rel="nofollow">Privacy Policy</a></li>
<li><a class="cd8fc3ae092e82d4020ecc4f881de638d" href="about-us.html" rel="nofollow">About Us</a></li>
</ul></div></div><div class="col-md-3">
<h3 class="z0b3c4586b2d8b391ee873941b00acd33 font-weight-bold">Connect</h3>
<hr>
<div class="social"><p class="sub">Follow us</p>
<a href="https://www.facebook.com/WaltzConcrete" class="y55f7b5da6598b8beb377675ed43d2faf facebook"  rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-facebook"></i></a>
<a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCzUsLOk5mYmA74pBeFmcU9w" class="y55f7b5da6598b8beb377675ed43d2faf youtube"   rel="nofollow"><i class="fa fa-youtube"></i></a>
</div>
</div></div>
<hr>
</div>
</footer><script type="text/javascript">
document.addEventListener('DOMContentLoaded', function() {
var dropdowns = document.querySelectorAll('.dropdown-hover');
function showDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'block';
}
function hideDropdown() {
var dropdownMenu = this.querySelector('.dropdown-menu');
dropdownMenu.style.display = 'none';
}
function handleClick(event) {
var target = event.target;
window.location.href = target.getAttribute('href');
}
dropdowns.forEach(function(dropdown) {
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseenter', showDropdown);
dropdown.addEventListener('mouseleave', hideDropdown);
var dropdownMenu = dropdown.querySelector('.dropdown-toggle');
dropdownMenu.addEventListener('click', handleClick);
});
});
</script>
</footer>
</body>
</html>
